Jay?
Jay, I know this gonna sound strange...
but I don't remember
anything from last night.
Jay?
Oh, my God.
Detective Jay Burgess,
one of the heroes...
from the Charleston
Police Station fire, is dead.
Police apparently received a 911 call
from an unidentified woman...
who spent the night
at Burgess' house.
Police aren't yet saying
if foul play was involved.
We will continue to bring you
more as this story unfolds.
Sue Share for Channel 8 News.
Detective, can you tell me
what happened?
Do you have any idea
how Jay died?
My wife and I watch you
almost every night, Ms. Shelley.
Thank you.
TVN says you're the number one
news reporter in Charleston.
- My, my.
- Yes, I've been very fortunate.
I was asking you...
Truth be told, I'm surprised CNN
or Fox hasn't scooped you up yet.
I bet you end up
on one of those national broadcasts.
Because it's the same
everywhere, isn't it?
It's just easier for people
to hear bad news...
when they're looking
at a pretty face.
Look, I'm just trying
to understand here.
Do you think Jay died
from respiratory failure...
or heart attack?
Actually, Ms. Shelley,
we were hoping you could tell us.
This isn't exactly your first brush
with this type of incident, is it?
Sorry, I'm Bill Alexander,
Ms. Shelley's attorney.
Your station manager said...
that I'm at your disposal
as long as you need.
Thank you.
Quite frankly, I was surprised that
Sam thought I needed an attorney...
but now I'm actually
glad that he suggested it.
Well, since we're all here...
why don't we go
into the interrogation room.
Just to be clear,
I'm not just giving a statement.
I mean, this is an interrogation...
so you see me
as some sort of suspect.
Well, shall we?
How well did you know
Jay Burgess?
He had given me
a lead on a story, that was it.
When?
Five years ago
right after the fire.
- Were you intimate?
- You don't have to answer that.
No, I wasn't.
- Not until you got the story.
- Again.
No. Not at all.
He did hit on me...
but I heard he was a player
and I just wasn't interested.
- Not that kind of girl?
- That's completely unnecessary.
And then yesterday
out of the blue, he called.
- Britt Shelley.
- Britt, it's Jay Burgess.
Oh, Detective Burgess,
it's been way too long.
Yeah, it has.
Said he had another story for me.
A big one.
But he needed to tell me
about it in person.
My partner on the force, Patty,
passed a few weeks back.
It's hit me hard,
harder than I expected.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It just got me thinking about life
and how short it is...
and, you know, if a man can right
the wrongs that he's done...
well, he should try,
you know, before it's too late.
I don't know
if this means anything or not...
but I remember a man watching us
while we were there.
- Had you ever seen this man before?
- No.
No, I thought maybe he was a fan.
A fan.
Or maybe he recognized Jay
from the police station fire.
Just the way he was looking at us
was so careful not to look at us.
It was strange.
I'm guessing you'll help our sketch
artist come up with a rendering?
- Probably.
- Great.
Mighty convenient, though,
a guy watching you at a bar...
and you happen to notice
and then Burgess happens to die.
You know, I'm a reporter.
That's what I do.
I'm trained to focus on details.
Is that why you left the bar?
Because of this man?
No.
You know what,
straight up, Britt, if...
I prefer to talk about this in private.
Is it all right if we go
to my apartment? It's up the road.
You know what,
all I wanna do is talk.
Scout's honor.
So, what was this big secret?
Okay.
Actually, I never found out.
Everything after that is cloudy.
- What do you mean, cloudy?
- I mean, I don't remember anything.
I can't remember a thing.
You can't remember what?
- Remember taking your clothes off?
- No.
- Getting into his bed?
So you can't remember having sex?
That's the thing.
I don't know that we did.
I know what it looks like
but I don't think...
Yeah, you weren't interested because
you're not that kind of girl.
All right, I don't think I should
allow my client to continue.
I don't understand
how one glass of wine...
could knock me out like that.
One glass.
It doesn't make any sense.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
The date-rape drug.
That's the only possible explanation.
Okay, I get it that you're playing
the good cop, bad cop thing...
but blink if you hear me.
Oh, we hear you, Ms. Shelley.
We hear you fine.
You just don't believe me.
You don't believe me at all.
Look at this.
As the investigation into the death
of Jay Burgess continues...
Not another story about Jay's death.
I know you were big heroes,
but how much more is there to say?
A lot.
The woman he was with
was none other than Britt Shelley.
- From the news?
- Yeah.
Unfortunately
I took a shower this morning...
so we felt it unnecessary
to test for rape.
I have no recollection
of being violated.
- Were you intoxicated, Ms. Shelley?
- No.
I did submit a urine sample
this morning...
to test for so-called
date-rape drugs.
These substances tend to disappear
quickly from the body...
so it's unlikely, at this point,
that anything will be detected.
- She thinks she was drugged?
- I guess so.
You're interested in this
because Jay was your friend?
Or you wish you could
unretire from the force...
and solve
this juicy little mystery?
Doing that
would require you to be sober.
Don't start, Miranda.
I can see why
you're so fascinated in all of this.
I mean, the idea of Britt Shelley...
waking up
next to Jay's cold, dead body.
It's not like I care
one way or another...
but you really can't escape
the irony, can you?
No, you can't.
I wonder if Candy's watching.
As Channel 8...
Poor Jay.
Police have not indicated whether
foul play was involved...
Did you know him
when you were a DA?
I knew everyone personally
when I was a DA.
- But Jay and I were friends.
- You're not going to the funeral.
The story is a little sordid.
You don't know where it might lead.
- And with your nomination pending...
- No, no, I won't go to the funeral.
I can't have my name
linked to it right now.
When the coroner
releases his report...
it will help shed some light
on what actually happened.
I wonder if this has to do
with that story she covered...
about the police station fire
five years ago.
Ms. Shelley,
doesn't this remind you...
of the story
that made your career...
about a certain arson investigator,
Raley Gannon?
- There were no drugs in that case.
- There were similarities.
I don't think it's a stretch to say
you buried Mr. Gannon in the media.
If he happens to be watching
this right now...
what do you think
might be going through his head?
There you have it, folks.
The mystery continues...
and we will bring you more
as this story unfolds.
Thank you for sending
that attorney over, Sam.
No problem. Did he help?
He was fine.
I wanted to let you know,
I'm gonna come in to work tomorrow.
Shouldn't you wait
until you feel better?
Come on, you know me.
Work's the only thing
that's gonna make me better.
I would love to have you back
at work tomorrow.
Trust me, we're dying without you.
Hey, you need me and I need
to work so it's a win-win, right?
Yeah, it would be.
Problem is the suits upstairs
have a different take on this.
The public's had their fill of scandal
and the people of Charleston...
might not appreciate
seeing you on TV again so soon.
So, what?
I'm just supposed to sit on my couch
and watch someone else do my job?
Give it a couple of days,
let it shake out. See what's what.
Are you home alone tonight?
You don't have much
in the family department.
But you shouldn't be alone.
Yeah, no, I have a friend over here
taking care of me.
I'm fine, don't worry.
Good night.
- Yeah. Oh, thanks.
- Here you go.
This is the sketch of the guy
she said she saw at the bar.
The phantom stalker.
Right.
Come on,
this guy is totally nondescript.
This could be a picture
of my landlord.
Does she seriously expect us
to believe that's a real guy?
Come on.
Reporter is turning out
to be a pain in the ass.
Thought she'd be too upset
to take a drug test.
Much less go public.
Well, if she's planning
any more surprises...
we'll be the first to know.
Shut up. Get up, get up.
Turn it off!
- I don't know who you are.
- Shut up.
- Shut up and turn it off.
- I don't remember anything.
What are you doing?
Get up. Get up.
- Help!
- Shut up. Shut up.
Raley Gannon?
- What are you doing?
- Tell me about Jay Burgess.
- Tell you what?
- What happened last night?
- I have no idea.
- Did you kill him?
- Did I...?
- Did you?
- Are you...?
- Did you kill him?
Did you kill him?
Are you out of your mind?
Look, if you could just loosen up
these ropes...
I will tell you
whatever you want to know.
You think you can bargain with me?
Interesting choice.
Oh, come on,
it's really uncomfortable.
Switching tactics.
Expressing frustration.
Do you have any idea
what I have been through?
Attempting to elicit sympathy.
Strategy number three.
Rounding out the performance
with acting defiant.
You ran the victim playbook
in under 60 seconds.
Congratulations.
You get a big A for actress.
Cut the crap and answer me.
What do you wanna know?
So, Jave, let's talk motive.
Why does a beautiful,
successful reporter...
kill a playboy cop?
I don't really think
it's all that complicated.
Burgess has a thing for her,
calls her up, asks her out.
Maybe she knows he's a "love them
and leave them" type of guy.
Maybe she doesn't.
Either way, they meet...
he whispers all the right things
in her ear and she falls for it.
Thinks they got some kind
of real connection.
She's a loner so letting him in
emotionally, that's a big freaking deal.
They do the deed
and he goes back to his old self.
Maybe even laughs
at her gullibility.
She's pissed.
She feels totally betrayed.
She snaps. Waits for him
to fall asleep, she kills him.
And she sets it up...
to look like a crime
she once reported on...
No, she did that after the fact...
because she figured
it would probably throw us off.
I should've known when I saw
the empty bottle of Scotch.
- It didn't make any sense.
- What didn't make sense?
I hate Scotch...
and I'm not exactly in the habit
of drinking myself into oblivion.
I like to be in control.
I believe that.
Why would Jay slip me the drug
at the Wheelhouse...
then make it look like we drank
at the apartment?
Someone else
had to have done it.
All right.
That's enough for now.
I'll sleep on the bed.
You get the floor.
Word of advice,
never look in the direction...
you're gonna strike
before you strike it.
Always follow a kick in the groin
with a shot to the chin.
Not surprising that you know
so much about hand-to-hand combat.
Don't you get
why I brought you here?
Because you killed Jay Burgess...
and you wanna know how close
the cops are to figuring that out.
I just needed to make sure
that you were telling the truth.
Now I know what happened to you...
and what happened to me
aren't isolated incidents.
- What are you talking about?
- Think it through.
Five years ago, someone arranged
for me to wake up next to a dead body.
Two nights ago, someone
did the exact same thing to you.
I think we were set up
by the same person.
The question is, who and why?
You need some help?
You got it.
I forgot to tell you.
I saw on the news that cop who died,
he was your dad's partner, right?
Yeah, for almost 10 years.
- When was the last time you saw him?
- Jay?
A month ago.
Dad's funeral.
He was actually really upset.
You know, it was actually
kind of weird to see him like that.
Listen, honey, I'm not gonna be home
for lunch today.
- You're not working through again?
- I'm afraid so. I'm sorry.
Okay, we're done. All done.
Good job, buddy.
Eggs?
You... You kidnap me,
you interrogate me, and now eggs?
I told you.
I needed to know
what really happened.
- I want to make sure that...
- I was telling the truth.
And now you are.
Fine, don't eat. I don't care.
- The beard's new.
- So?
It suits you. It's very menacing.
I got you some clothes.
Can't have you going to town
dressed like that.
People will get suspicious.
If this kidnapping thing
doesn't work out for you...
you could always become
a personal shopper.
You thought what happened to you
five years ago...
and what happened to me
the other night were somehow related.
Our stories are similar.
Especially considering
they both involve Jay.
Charleston's a very small town.
Jay knew everybody,
everybody knew Jay.
So it's not surprising he could've
been involved in both situations.
Second of all,
only one element is really the same.
We both woke up
next to a dead body.
That's a pretty big one element,
don't you think?
I will admit there is that one
glaring similarity...
but all the other circumstances
are different.
You got drunk
and had sex with a drug addict.
Nobody slipped you anything
in your drink.
Actually, I always suspected
that somebody did.
- Don't look at me like that.
- This is the way I look...
when someone tells a story
that strains credibility.
I don't care. That's what happened.
Someone slipped you
the date-rape drug?
Apparently,
it's not just for women anymore.
Okay. Who?
Yeah, well,
that's where it gets complicated.
I'm listening.
Okay.
The police station fire.
- Candy, are you all right?
- I'm fine, Jay, I'm okay.
Help her.
- Ground floor's clear.
- The basement?
I don't know.
- George?
- All right, we better check.
- You can't go back there.
- Candy, stay here.
Pat, let's go.
- Raley.
- Get out of here. Get back, okay?
Jay, George and Pat
went back in there.
We got three cops inside.
Bring him out. Let's go.
Bring him out.
Put him on the ground.
Easy, easy. Is he breathing, Jay?
- I don't think he's breathing.
- Get out of here.
Pat, Jay, get out of here.
I was the investigator in charge.
All the evidence suggested
that Cleveland Jones...
the one fatality,
had actually set the fire.
Seemed like just desserts.
I just had a few loose ends
to wrap up.
It wasn't my story...
but I do remember my boss waited
a while for that arson report.
Yeah, because I was waiting on Jay.
Come on, Jay, I came all the way
down here to get it.
- Yeah, I know, man.
- I can't do the report...
until I finish the investigation.
I can't finish until I get the Jones file.
Look at this place.
I can't even find a frigging pen.
His autopsy said cause of death
was actually a skull fracture.
I'm not clear whether he got
that before or after the fire.
- Any idea?
- He didn't get it before.
Maybe he hit his head
when he was trying to get out.
Really, man, who cares, you know?
I mean, the guy
was in a revolving door to juvie.
- I mean, armed robbery, assault.
- But not arson.
He learned a new trick
at juvenile hall.
I just need this file
and then I can close the case.
Raley, I know you're trying
to do your job.
I'm trying to get out of here early.
- Yeah, I know. Your party.
- Yeah.
This place
that I'm house-sitting, it's huge.
It's worth it to come by
to see this monstrosity.
- Jay, I can't.
- Everybody's gonna be there.
George, Pat, Candy.
- It's that Haley's got this thing...
- Bring her.
I can't. She's going away.
She's going to visit her sister.
I told you that.
Yeah, I just forgot.
It's perfect, though. Why don't you
just come by for a drink?
I tell you what,
you come by for a drink...
I will find the file,
I will bring it to the fire house...
first thing in the morning.
What do you say?
- You're gonna bring it to me?
- Yeah.
Why do you care so much
if I come?
It's just, you know, since the fire,
I'm feeling a little sentimental.
Might be kind of nice
to have the whole gang together.
- Okay.
- All right.
- I'll see you later.
- Hey, can you pick up Candy?
She needs a lift.
Always something with you,
isn't it?
- See you.
- Yeah.
You look good, Raley. Happy.
Do I? I guess I am.
You look good too. New dress?
Not any newer
than last time you saw it.
- You lost weight?
- Ten pounds, actually.
Yep, another one
of Jay's free-for-alls.
Don't play with your food,
just drink it.
They'll let anybody in there.
- George.
- Hey, glad you made it.
Hey, Pat.
Hey, where's our gracious host?
Jay's right over there.
Where do you think?
- Well, I'm empty. Raley?
- No, thanks.
- Suit yourself.
- I'll take one.
I'm down with that.
Your friend thought
you might like this.
I hear you're a fireman.
I like firemen.
Look, thanks for the drink,
but I'm engaged.
Oh, yeah?
Are you sure?
That's not usually the response
I get, but yeah, I'm sure.
Last week I priced out minivans.
I got it.
But there's no reason
why we can't talk, is there?
I mean, at least take the drink.
Cheers.
So the girl who walked out
on the terrace, you didn't know her?
Never seen her before in my life.
- And she turned out to be a...
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I never knew that she pursued you.
You never knew a lot of things.
Okay, so she gave you a drink...
you took a couple of sips,
and then what?
And then I have no idea.
The next morning I woke up...
we were naked...
and she was dead.
I found Jay.
Since we were kids,
Jay was able to think fast.
She's a junkie,
nobody's gonna miss her.
- You know this girl?
- Yeah, I've seen her around.
Hey, be cool, don't worry about it.
We're gonna take care of it.
And he promised me that everything
was gonna be just fine.
I just woke up next to a dead body
and Jay Burgess promised me...
that everything
was gonna be just fine.
Yeah, but I don't get it.
Why didn't you include this
in your statement...
that you thought
somebody had drugged you?
I wanted to.
Candy convinced me not to.
Candy?
Okay, just to be clear, we're
talking about Cassandra Mellers...
who's about to be confirmed...
as the youngest female
federal judge in the country?
Yeah, we called her Candy.
She's an old friend.
Yeah, at the time she was
the Charleston DA. Talking to you...
Would've seriously jeopardized
her career. I know.
We'd always relied on each other.
I'm telling you, I don't remember.
She must've put something
in my drink.
That may be true but the problem is
it will be hard to verify.
Then I'll take a drug test.
Look, Raley, say you were drugged.
Chances
of the date-rape substance...
remaining in your system
this long are slim.
By asking, you're casting suspicion
on yourself.
You're admitting
you don't remember...
- what happened.
- I don't.
Which will make people wonder
if you have something to hide.
Now, look at it the other way.
Say you don't ask for the test.
In the meantime, the girl’s death
is ruled an accidental overdose.
That's it. It's over.
You'll be in the clear.
I know, I know.
I wish it were different.
You know, this story,
it wasn't originally my beat.
But then I started investigating
and Pat Wickham, George McGowan...
no one told me this.
You don't believe me?
Not like I give a damn what you think.
Because you have moral standards.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- I came clean fast.
Pat and George made sure the
investigation stayed under the radar.
My life might've actually
gotten back on track.
Until ace reporter Britt Shelley...
decided to build a career
on my story.
Things get worse for
fire inspector Raley Gannon...
as pressure mounts
for his resignation.
Police are questioning
Gannon's coworkers...
in connection with the death
of Suzi Monroe.
The coroner has not
released his report.
Mr. Gannon remains the only person
of interest in this case.
Get dressed.
Ms. Shelley, this is Bill Alexander,
your attorney.
This is the third time I've tried
to reach you this morning.
The police called.
The coroner's office
is going to announce...
Jay Burgess' cause of death,
and when that happens...
they may want to speak to you.
Would you please call me
and tell me where you are?
Thanks.
- George.
- What?
- You have company.
- Hi, Miranda.
What are you doing here, Pat?
Can we make this quick, please?
We have to be at the club.
I'll meet you there.
George, we need to talk.
What are you so jumpy about, Pat?
Jay's gone and nobody gives a damn
about your little secret.
You do, George.
If you don't, you really should.
Get a grip.
Britt Shelley's attorney
can't find her.
I bet she skipped town.
Think about it. She's a reporter,
she thinks someone drugged her.
She'll start
to put things together.
Things about me, things about you.
George?
Yeah.
Okay, thank you.
Britt Shelley's tox report.
No date-rape drug.
Surprise, surprise.
We gotta find this woman, man.
- She lies, she bails.
- She kills.
I just heard from the coroner.
You called it.
Jay Burgess got drunk and
someone smothered him in his sleep.
This case
is now officially a homicide.
- Take my car back to Charleston.
- What?
I'll figure out how to pick it up.
Come on, let's go.
You gotta get out of here.
Fine. But for the record,
you have no right to blame me.
For following the wrong story...
- or screwing up my life?
- What do you mean, the wrong story?
You know what,
all the evidence pointed to you.
I will not apologize
for doing my job.
You accused me of murder.
When the autopsy came back,
I reported it was an overdose.
It didn't matter.
By then nobody trusted me anymore.
You're not just talking
about your coworkers, are you?
- You're talking about that girl.
- Haley.
I tried to get an interview
with her...
We weren't just dating.
We were engaged.
Raley, I got a lead
and I followed it.
Exactly.
And who gave you that lead?
Five years ago, Jay did, right?
Mr. Everything's Gonna Be Fine.
That is how I first met him.
He came to me with your story
and told me he was sure...
you killed that girl.
- How did you know that I met him?
- Don't you get it?
Don't you see
the big picture here?
I've had five years
to put this together.
I've looked at it from every angle...
and along the way,
I found out a few things.
One, the party house,
it didn't belong to any friend.
Jay rented it under a fake name
so it couldn't be traced to him.
Two, the girl, Jay had known
she was a drug addict for years.
And three,
after realizing one and two...
it seemed obvious that Jay
must have contacted you.
My point being
that you missed the real story.
That Jay Burgess
carefully orchestrated all of it.
Getting you
to blast my face on the news...
was just the final nail
in the coffin.
It just... It doesn't make sense.
I mean, why would he try
to screw up your career...
and risk ruining his own?
That's exactly
what I wanted to know.
And I could only think of one thing.
The Cleveland Jones file.
What do you think
would be in that file...
that could possibly
be so terrible?
I wish I could tell you.
After I lost my job,
the arson investigator...
that took over the case closed it.
If he did get
the Cleveland Jones file...
he didn't include it
in the final report.
And then he bought a car
and a new house...
and took his wife
on a cruise to Mexico.
- So you think Jay paid him off?
- Someone did.
Until yesterday,
I always thought Jay acted alone.
Then it hit me that Jay
must have had an accomplice.
And that accomplice killed him...
Because he was gonna finally
tell me the truth.
- Do you have a phone?
- No.
Of course not.
You do.
You took my purse?
Needed to make it look
like you left on your own.
Good. That will go over well
with the cops since they love me.
Who are you calling?
Well, if I was following
the wrong story...
maybe it's not too late
for me to get the right one.
Hi, Sam, it's me.
- Britt, where are you?
- I didn't skip town.
I don't think you understand
how serious this is.
Oh, yeah, no, I do, I do.
I'm trying to get to the bottom of it.
- It's about the police station fire.
- What about it?
I don't have the details yet...
but Jay Burgess' death
relates back to it.
- And you know this how?
- I'm gonna need your help.
Track down the paperwork on Jones,
the guy that started the fire.
Don't bother looking at the fire
investigation report. It's not there.
Okay, listen to me, Britt.
Sam, you gotta trust me on this.
This is really good.
I'm gonna save my ass.
I'm gonna break open a story.
Yeah, from where? Jail?
Coroner's report came.
Jay Burgess was murdered.
It's official.
They've actually issued
a warrant for your arrest.
You gotta turn yourself in.
Britt, are you listening to me?
Yeah. Yeah, I heard you.
- You got her?
- Got her.
You'll want these. Directions.
I don't understand
why you won't come.
What happened to me is confirmation
of what happened to you.
- If we go to the police...
- You kidding?
I don't trust the cops anymore.
I sure as hell don't trust you.
You destroyed my life. You think I'd
give you the chance to do it again?
I listened to your story.
You have selective memory.
Back when I was reporting on you
I begged you for an interview.
I gave you the opportunity
to tell your side but you wouldn't.
- Shut up.
- No.
You lay low and let things pass by.
- Just shut up.
- No, you should've fought back.
You should've fought.
If not for yourself, for your fiancée.
You have no idea
how much I wanted to fight for her.
No idea.
Raley, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I know exactly why I'm alone.
What's your excuse?
Damn it!
It's okay.
So are you guys close
to catching her?
I mean, Jay was my dad's partner...
so he was kind of like a father
to me himself.
Yeah, we understand. Really.
We got an APB out on her.
- Every cop in the state is on high alert.
- Great.
Good.
You know, she comes across
as very earnest and innocent...
but my father always told me that
those were the most dangerous type.
Just that...
Okay.
Are you okay?
I should take you to the hospital,
I think you're still in shock.
No.
I'm fine, it's just a little cut.
Guessing you couldn't see who...
Two men, black Mercedes,
that's all I could tell.
Your station manager, you think
maybe his phone was bugged?
Not his, probably mine.
The fact someone knows I'm looking
for the Jones file and tried to kill me...
means we're getting close.
Those guys after you
think you're dead. Works in our favor.
Gotta be another way
to figure out what's in that file.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm...
I...
I just need a minute.
Britt?
- Hey, Raley?
- Yeah?
Less menacing?
What?
You going somewhere?
Yeah, Jay's funeral.
Well, I was thinking we've been going
about this the wrong way.
What do you mean?
There must be someone who knows
what was going on with Cleveland.
He must have been close
to somebody.
So why don't you let me
ask the questions?
Why?
You're sure he'll open up if you
woo him with your wily feminine ways?
No, I'm a good reporter and collecting
information is what I do for a living.
Thank you so much for that
backhanded, sexist non-compliment.
Can't you read?
Mr. Jones,
you probably don't remember me.
Met years ago. I was investigating
the fire that killed your son.
I remember you.
Like I said then, he set it, he died...
and sometimes justice
has a way of taking care of itself.
- We're not sure that's what happened.
- Either way, the boy died.
We're not sure that he had to.
I'm Britt Shelley, news reporter.
I know who you are.
I got a TV.
Right now it's telling me you're the one
that killed that hero policeman.
All the more reason
I need your help.
I believe someone's trying
to frame me for murder.
They think I know a secret
about your son's death.
Send me away and neither of us
will find out what it is.
It can't be easy. Losing a child.
Cleveland was no child.
I couldn't keep up with all the times
that boy was in and out of jail.
Rape, robbery.
Pretty sure
he had his very own personal cell.
Last time I saw him I told him
I wasn't gonna bail him out no more.
Next thing I get a call from the police
telling me he was dead.
What was the name
of the officer who called?
I don't remember.
You must have been in shock.
Not really.
Sure wish I got back the lighter,
though.
Cleveland really loved that thing.
- The lighter?
- Yeah.
My daddy bought it for him.
It had this...
This picture on it of a half-naked girl,
she was, like, wearing a...
What was it? A red bikini.
Every time Cleveland saw that thing
he would... He would laugh.
Didn't come back with his stuff,
though.
I asked the cops about it
and they said they never saw it.
The day that your son died,
he was arrested.
Do you know what for?
I don't know.
He used to like to hang out
with his loser friends...
down in Hampton Parkway.
I wouldn't be surprised
if they got him defacing property.
- What about the skull fracture?
- What?
Skull fracture. Didn't they tell you?
So the question is, how did Cleveland
get the skull fracture?
Why didn't the cops tell his father?
Who interrogated him?
Jay, George and Pat.
They claimed he was fine
when he left the room.
The next thing they know
the station was on fire.
Well, Jay's dead.
Pat Wickham died a couple
months ago, that leaves George.
Most likely suspect.
How'd he know
Jay was gonna come clean?
Well, I'll be sure to ask him.
I gotta get going.
Hey, I'm gonna do a little research.
I saw a computer in the motel office.
Are you kidding?
You're not going.
There's a warrant out.
The last thing you need to be doing
is hanging out.
So? You want me to sit here
and watch television all day?
That's why we got a room
with cable.
Can you clear my schedule?
I've decided to go to Jay's funeral.
Left, left, left.
God bless
and peace be with all of you.
Thank you.
It was a beautiful service.
- Miss you around the station.
- Thanks for coming.
- Coming from Atlanta, I hear.
- Yeah.
George.
Raley.
It's good to see you.
I was so hoping you'd be here.
- Candy, I'm so sorry about Jay.
- Me too.
I missed you. I tried to find you,
but you didn't leave much of a trail.
I just needed
not to be found for a while.
- Congratulations on the nomination.
- Thank you.
I can't say I'm surprised.
It means a lot to me.
Judge Mellers.
Forgive me,
but you do have another appointment.
- I'm sorry, Raley, I have to...
- It's okay.
I know this may not be the time
or the place...
but I'm not gonna get another
chance and it's always bothered me.
After Suzi Monroe died...
maybe I didn't advise you well
about the drug test.
Maybe...
Maybe I made a mistake.
If you need anything...
I mean it, anything.
Thank you.
Take care.
Raley.
- George McGowan.
- It's been a while.
Jay would've appreciated
that you came out of hiding for this.
No doubt.
- I heard you've been doing well lately.
- I fell in love.
With a woman? Or money?
Well, I guess that the marriage
didn't exactly work out as I planned.
Too bad.
Add one more thing
to your list of regrets, huh?
Something on your mind, Raley?
Yeah, there is. Jay's murder.
May I help you, ma'am?
Yeah, I was wondering
if I could use your computer.
Actually we have an entire
business center set up right there.
Thanks.
You might need to plug it in first.
I don't know any more than you do.
Apparently, that newswoman killed
him after they got back from the bar.
He met her at a bar?
I don't remember that in the news.
He told me he was going to do it.
He was thinking of retiring, gonna
convince her to do a story on him.
- That really why?
- Yeah.
Or did he want to
get something off his chest?
Like what?
Hey, Pat.
Come here.
Do you have any idea what Jay
might've wanted to tell a reporter?
No, no. I have no clue.
Hey.
Let's see.
Fried shrimp.
And... And salad?
That's what you got?
- I thought you'd want...
- Fried shrimp, good call.
- So did you talk to George?
- Yeah.
George and Pat Jr. looked
like they had something to hide.
Well, you may not be wrong.
Read that.
- What, you went out?
- Oh, come on, just read it.
It says here that five years ago
in Hampton Park...
Pat Wickham Jr. was attacked.
Must've been how he got the scar. His
dad said he got it in some bar brawl.
The kid never seemed like the type.
And Hampton Park, that's where
Cleveland Jones used to hang out.
Some coincidence.
So you think
we should go talk to Pat Jr.?
Absolutely.
God, I always hated that park.
Full of dealers and junkies.
Haley cut through there
on her morning run.
I begged her to find another route.
You know, I've actually been meaning
to say something to you about that. I...
I realized that my story is what caused
you to lose that relationship with her.
And I just...
I just want you to know
that I am truly, truly sorry.
Yeah, well, I guess I've been telling
myself that for the past five years.
That it was all your fault.
If you hadn't kept my face
in the news...
there wouldn't have been
so much pressure.
And she and I,
we would've been okay.
Truth is, I know it's not that simple.
You know,
you said that I should've fought.
- If not for myself then for my fiancée.
- Raley, I should...
The thing is, it was Haley
who begged me not to fight.
She wanted it
to just all go away on its own.
What did you want?
I wanted her to stay.
I wanted to make her happy.
And she left anyway.
She couldn't stick it out.
She wasn't like you.
She wasn't a fighter.
Yeah, got it.
All right, Raley Gannon just surfaced
at Jay Burgess' funeral.
- Any idea where he'll turn up next?
- Yeah, boss gave me an address.
Well, judge,
I have to say it's an honor to meet you.
I think the whole city is excited
about your pending nomination.
My wife keeps telling me
it's a great leap for Southern women.
Thank you.
You're wondering
why I asked you here.
Well, yeah.
I hear you have family in Columbia.
Yeah, my wife's sister
and some cousins.
You've been inquiring about
transferring to the Columbia P.D.
I know a lot of people.
Some of whom may be able
to make that happen.
Bypassing the usual
bureaucratic channels and such.
Well, that would be...
I would be much obliged.
But in return
I need to ask something of you.
- Off the record, do you understand?
- Yeah.
I was hoping not to get involved in this,
but circumstances are such that...
it seems unavoidable.
I need you to tell me everything about
the Jay Burgess investigation.
I know this is highly irregular...
but I'm worried that someone
may be wrongfully blamed for this.
And I can't let that happen again.
He's home.
Let's wait a minute,
see if a light comes on.
I think I should be the one
to go talk to him.
I've been thinking.
You should really try and make
a transition to a bigger market.
You're beautiful, you're smart.
You're number one in Charleston,
but that's what? A few thousand?
It's nothing.
If you went national,
you'd be seen by millions.
- I have had a couple of big offers.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- So, what's the problem?
Well, for one, in a big market
the competition's tougher...
and the expectations are higher.
- So what?
- So, what if I can't hack it?
I mean, I don't have some
big, happy family to fall back on.
My parents are dead
and there's nobody else.
So if I take a big job and fail at it,
then how would I support myself?
So your concern
is financial security?
Well, yeah.
- You'll have to be smart.
- Yeah.
- And cautious.
- Exactly.
- And gutless.
- What?
I'm serious. No guts, no glory.
You're not going for the glory,
so really, who needs the guts?
Did you just insult me?
It's almost 11:00 at night.
Where's he going?
I don't know. Let's find out.
- What is this?
- It's a gay club.
Out here?
You think
it's easy being gay in the South?
Especially if you're a cop.
- Hey.
- Hey there.
- Hey, how's it going?
Haven't seen you in a while.
Hey, fellas. You don't mind
if I talk to my friend, do you?
What are you doing here?
Following me?
No, I'm not,
but we need to talk to you.
Who's we?
- Are you with her?
- Hi.
Mr. Wickham, we were wondering
if you could help us.
What exactly really happened
to your face?
My face?
Why? Raley knows I got into a fight.
Nice story. Try again, Pat.
Look, the truth always comes out.
Better if you just tell us now, talk to us.
- Tell us about the police station fire.
- Screw off.
- What about Hampton Park?
- Nobody knows about any of that.
Just don't go there, please.
Get down!
Get in the car, get in the car.
Go, go!
Well, you're lucky.
That bullet barely nicked you.
- Yeah, well, it still hurts.
- I know.
- Nice necklace.
- Thank you.
- It doesn't exactly seem like your style.
- It's not.
- Then why do you wear it?
- Sentimental.
From your parents?
- Old boyfriend?
- No.
My bosses gave it to me after I won
number one three years in a row.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- So I get it now.
- Get what?
Why you'll never leave
your job at the station.
Financial security my ass.
You, my friend,
are seriously full of crap.
So is that your version
of small talk or foreplay?
I've seen you in action.
With Louis Jones, Pat Jr.
You're a great interviewer.
You could go anywhere
and be a star.
Says the man
whose TV only gets three channels.
But you won't.
Because you need to stay.
Your parents are all gone.
You avoid getting close to people.
You'll never quit,
you'll never try something else...
because your job is the one true
long-term relationship you've got.
You look deep in thought.
I was remembering when we met.
God, you were so unattainable.
Sailing high above
with the socialite crowd...
barely knowing
peons like me even existed.
When you agreed to marry me,
I couldn't believe it.
And I couldn't figure out why.
You were a hero, George.
Every girl wants a hero.
And I fell in love with you.
Are you still?
The night you told me the truth
about the fire...
something just changed.
Everything that I thought you were and
everything I thought you could be...
was based on a lie.
And I felt betrayed.
And I knew
I'd never let you betray me again.
I'm sorry, George.
- Hey, did you see this?
- What?
Pat Jr's attack
happened five years ago.
- September 14th.
- So?
So the police station fire happened
five years ago, September 15th.
Cleveland Jones was at both.
Cleveland was a redneck.
And rednecks aren't fond
of the gay population.
And cops aren't too fond
of rednecks who beat up cops' kids.
Do you think Pat Sr.
beat up Cleveland?
Or George, or Jay, or all of them.
Pat, please don't forget
to fix the stroller today.
Oh, my God. Pat?
They're here for me. It's all right.
- Should I stay?
- I'm fine, honey.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, go ahead, it's okay.
Are you gonna leave too?
You guys wanna come in?
I know why you ran.
It must have been hard
living a lie all these years.
It's not like I had a choice.
My father and George used to tell
homo jokes around the dinner table.
And I used to laugh along.
And one day my dad caught me
in my bedroom with a friend.
And if my mom hadn't stopped him,
I swear to God, he would've killed me.
Secrets cost you a lot, huh?
Your freedom, integrity,
even your face.
Cleveland Jones did that, didn't he?
In the park.
Him and two of his friends.
They used the end of a bat
like a pile driver in my mouth.
The surgeons
did the best they could but...
Wasn't good enough for your dad,
was it?
Yeah, maybe he still loved me.
Maybe.
He showed you some mug shots?
Yeah, Cleveland
was the only one I recognized.
What did he tell you
he was gonna do?
He just said that he and his friends
were gonna take care of it.
His friends?
You mean George and Jay.
They didn't want me testifying
in a trial.
So they just wanted to make sure
that Jones confessed.
How did the police station
fire happen?
I really don't know.
I was in the hospital for weeks,
I was in pain, I was on meds.
Anything that happened that night
no one ever talked to me about it.
You never bothered to tell
anybody else about what you knew?
They had gotten revenge for me
one way or another.
I owed them something.
I owed them.
And you just filled in one lie
for another, huh?
Well...
it's over now.
What are you gonna do? You can't...
Well, it's like she told you before.
The truth always comes out.
All you have control over is how.
Don't.
- Thirty-eight years.
- Ma'am?
Thirty-eight years I've been dreaming
about making my name in the law.
Other girls
were playing Barbie and dress up.
I was pretending
to be Clarence Darrow or John Jay.
After tomorrow, I bet some little girl
will be pretending to be you.
Maybe.
Pat Wickham Jr. shot twice
at close range late this afternoon.
Police are calling Britt Shelley
a person of interest.
What?
According to Wickham's wife, Shelley
was last seen with her husband.
We gotta do something.
I've got an idea,
but we have to split up.
Okay.
- Press conference in 30 minutes.
- I'll be ready.
- Good luck, judge.
- Thank you.
This is it.
Miranda?
I knew you'd show up.
I'd go with the long ones.
My clerk let you in.
- Thank you for trusting me.
- I don't trust you.
I trust Raley, and he told me
you have a story to tell me.
I know who killed Jay Burgess...
Pat Wickham Jr.
and Cleveland Jones.
Please.
Believe it or not
I'm actually kind of relieved.
You need to come clean, George.
Yeah, I guess so.
Five years ago Cleveland Jones
attacked Pat Jr. in Hampton Park.
Pat Sr. wanted justice but he didn't
want his son's sexual orientation out.
So he and Jay pick Cleveland up.
The three of you were gonna beat
him until he confessed.
But things didn't go according to plan,
did they, George?
One of you,
doesn't really matter which...
bashed the kid's skull
until he was dead.
To cover their tracks,
the cops started a fire.
Blaming Cleveland for it.
Pretended to be victims themselves
and helped everyone get out.
- Became heroes.
- Yeah.
I guess everything
would've been fine if I just let it rest.
- But you couldn't, could you?
- No, I couldn't.
The cops knew the only way to avoid
being exposed was to shut Raley up.
One way or another.
The girl at the party.
And then you found Suzi Monroe and
you sent her to hit on me and drug me.
Done anything for a fix.
She'd hump the couch.
And you made sure she OD'd.
Yeah. We'd been around long enough.
We knew how it was done.
When Raley woke up,
they told him to keep quiet.
But Jay made sure
it became big news.
Jay and me.
My newscast distracted the public and
assured that Raley would lose his job.
Then Jay bribed the new
arson investigator to close the case.
- So if all this is true, who killed Jay?
- George did.
Pat Sr's death
really shook Jay up...
so Jay called George
and said he wanted to come clean.
But George couldn't let that happen.
So he had Jay killed
and framed me for the murder.
You're right about everything,
except the last part.
I didn't kill Jay.
Actually, I thought that you had
murdered him and Pat Jr. for revenge.
And that you came here today
to kill me.
I'm a good judge, Britt.
Maybe even a great judge.
So believe me when I tell you...
sometimes the end
really does justify the means.
No.
Oh, my God.
You were there, weren't you?
What's going on?
You hadn't just gotten to the station
when the fire happened.
You had been there for a while.
Watching the interrogation.
You were in the room when they killed
Cleveland Jones, weren't you?
Put the gun on the desk, face down
on the floor, now. Do it now!
- On the floor.
- You know every cop in the city.
Wait a minute.
But these guys, they're different.
You and these guys go way back.
You grew up together. Right?
That's why you wanted to be there...
when they interrogated the bastard
that hurt Pat's son.
Maybe you started
with good intentions.
Maybe you thought you'd just come
and prosecute him yourself.
But instead you stayed...
and watched Jay, George and Pat
pummel him to death.
You knew that if Raley found out,
your career would be over.
You couldn't let that happen.
So that's where the cover-up began.
First it was Cleveland.
And then it was Suzi Monroe.
And then Jay.
And now it's my turn, right?
Well, I'm impressed.
They say many
highly successful people...
are actually
functioning lying psychopaths.
You are so very convincing.
She sold me, that's for sure.
- Britt, you okay?
- Yeah.
You have been looking out
for someone all these years.
But it wasn't me, was it?
Let's go, judge.
- This all your handiwork?
- Get moving.
Yeah, I learned a few things about
hand-to-hand combat.
Thank God you're okay.
- Hey, come on.
- Just a second.
Okay, I'll let you know.
- Hi.
God, I'm starving. Who was that?
Fire chief.
Offered to give my job back.
- That's great.
- Yeah, well, let him stew for a while.
Crab sandwich.
- Meatball hero.
- Nice work.
So how did it go at the station?
Great.
They want me back at work too.
With a hefty raise
and hour-long specials...
new big office, my own assistant.
- That sounds like a good offer.
- Yeah, it is.
I told them
I wanted to think about it.
I wanna check out some
of the national networks first.
That's a great idea.
Yeah, well, don't get too excited.
I kind of just wanna explore
my possibilities, you know.
Maybe I don't need the Charleston
station so much anymore.
- At least as a long-term relationship.
- No?
So, what do you need?
Don't tell anybody, but I kinda have
a thing for clean-shaven firemen.